[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "WP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NNS", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 4, "question": "What was that man really like?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "RB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 5, "answer": "He was somebody who didn't know any boundaries, really, that didn't quite clearly see the lines, the lines that all of us need to see in the light, a line between right and wrong.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 18, "question": "Why did you feel differently about your father?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 19, "answer": "I think because he -- he tried.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 29, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 30, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 32, "question": "Did you feel that when you finished it, that you -- when you closed the book and thought, That's my life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBD", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 33, "answer": "Yes, I did.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Saturday"], "PERSON": ["Donald Trump", "Bill Clinton"]}, "docId": "111112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 44, "question": "Why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 45, "answer": "Because I just thought of you as this funny guy who does Donald Trump and Bill Clinton on \"Saturday Night Live.\"", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", ":", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "IN", ":", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 48, "question": "What -- what's that done to your life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", ":", "WP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 49, "answer": "Well, it's -- that's a lot -- that's a lot of -- that's a lot to think about.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 51, "question": "I spent most of my life, I guess, recovering from moments like that, you know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBG", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 52, "answer": "ORGAN: And it went on.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "IN", "WRB", "PRP$", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 68, "question": "It does happen, you know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 69, "answer": "Do you have any theories yourself about why your mother...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 71, "question": "She'd been abused?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 72, "answer": "I think she was abused.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "CC", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "NN", "CC", ":", "CC", "JJR", "."], "qSentId": 77, "question": "As you got older, what was your relationship with your mother like?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJR", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 78, "answer": "Well, I -- I called her and said, I'm -- I'm in therapy for trauma and child abuse and -- and worse.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "PRP$", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 86, "question": "Did you have any more contact with her?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "RBR", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 87, "answer": "Not until her deathbed.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 88, "question": "And how did that make you feel, when she died?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 89, "answer": "I felt nothing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 90, "question": "I was very moved by my father, you know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 91, "answer": "Well, it's not surprising to me that you're so emotional about this.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 96, "question": "Why did you feel differently about your father?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 97, "answer": "I think because he -- he tried.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 101, "question": "Can I have a tissue or something?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 102, "answer": "Yes, sure.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 107, "question": "Was he aware of what your mother was doing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "WP", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 108, "answer": "I don't think so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 109, "question": "He -- he was never there, you know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 110, "answer": "He was apologetic for his own negligence towards you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Clinton"]}, "docId": "111112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "CD", "WDT", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RBS", "NN", "IN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 152, "question": "Which was your favorite?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "VBD", "PRP$", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 153, "answer": "I guess Clinton is the one that -- that you get the most mileage out of.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ":"], "qSentId": 157, "question": "Where?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 158, "answer": "Oh...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 167, "question": "... colonoscopy?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 168, "answer": "No, just right before it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 178, "question": "So you do do it, you say?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 179, "answer": "Once in a while.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Donald Trump"]}, "docId": "111112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "JJ", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 189, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 190, "answer": "My favorite was Donald Trump.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 214, "question": "What do you make of his impression?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 215, "answer": "Well, he's been amazing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 228, "question": "Where go you get the ability to do impressions from, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "IN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 229, "answer": "I guess from my mom.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 231, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 232, "answer": "Really good.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNS", ",", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 239, "question": "Who would she do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 240, "answer": "Coaches, teachers, people in the neighborhood.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 243, "question": "And would make you laugh?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 244, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 248, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 249, "answer": "It just would change her.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 265, "question": "Have you been able to forgive her, in your mind?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBN", "JJ", "TO", "JJ", "PRP$", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 266, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 283, "question": "Well, I was going to ask you, were you ever high when you were on the air?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 284, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN"], "qSentId": 289, "question": "Never tempted?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 290, "answer": "No!", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 299, "question": "Are you clean now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 300, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "IN", "DT", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 301, "question": "You don't drink or take drugs at all?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "CC", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 302, "answer": "Well, I haven't done as well as I wanted to with that, but it's been going pretty well.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 315, "question": "Are you happier than you've been before?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "JJR", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 316, "answer": "I think so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 322, "question": "Do you think \"Saturday Night Live\" co-stars will be shocked by this book?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "VBZ", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 323, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Saturday"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 326, "question": "Did they know about your mother and stuff?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 327, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 333, "question": "How bad was the incident?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 334, "answer": "It was pretty damned bad.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 337, "question": "From the studio?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 338, "answer": "Actually, from -- I think that in the book it says the offices.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 350, "question": "How could this have been going on with this guy, who just seems like he's the happiest, funniest guy you'd ever meet?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "DT", "VB", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", ",", "JJS", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 351, "answer": "It did.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "``", "JJ", "PRP", "EX", "NNP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 355, "question": "What are you doing career-wise now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "JJ", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 356, "answer": "Well, I'm doing \"Are We There Yet?\"", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Truman Capote"]}, "docId": "111112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 362, "question": "What ambitions do you have professionally and personally?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "CC", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 363, "answer": "I just want to play Truman Capote on Broadway.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 408, "question": "Do you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 409, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "WP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "RB", ",", "IN", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 417, "question": "What was that man really like?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "RB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 418, "answer": "He was somebody who didn't know of any boundaries really, that didn't quite clearly see the lines, the lines that all of us need to see in life, the line between right and wrong.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 422, "question": "What went wrong?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 423, "answer": "BRAMOFF: Well, I think that with me, a couple things went wrong.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 440, "question": "I mean, that to me was -- it isn't worse than the corruption, but it certainly left a pretty bad taste when you read that, you know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "TO", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 441, "answer": "I'm not going to defend my e-mails.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 451, "question": "What do you think was the worst thing you did?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBD", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 452, "answer": "Well, a number of things.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 464, "question": "Did you know as you were doing it you were breaking the law?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 465, "answer": "I didn't consciously feel I was doing that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ":"], "qSentId": 475, "question": "H many other people at the time were crossing the line do you really think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 476, "answer": "Well, there are a lot of lines and a lot of these lines --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 479, "question": "What would you guess from your knowledge of the system?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 480, "answer": "A healthy percentage.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 481, "question": "What kind of percentage?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 482, "answer": "Twenty.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 483, "question": "Twenty percent of every lobbyist was doing the same kind of thing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 484, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 486, "question": "BRAMOFF: Have been held to account?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "NNP", "VBN", "VBN", "TO", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 487, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 531, "question": "What was your reaction to that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 532, "answer": "He's the leader of the free world.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 535, "question": "Come out and say he's my best friend and, you know, I was hand in glove with him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "JJS", "NN", "CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 536, "answer": "It's completely implausible he wouldn't have been aware with you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", ":", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 539, "question": "How could he not know who you were?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 540, "answer": "Well, I -- yes, I can't speak for him but he's a politician.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Congress", "Justice Department"]}, "docId": "111112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", "VBN", "VBD", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "``", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "CC", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 546, "question": "Where were you, how did you know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 547, "answer": "I guess what happened was there was an article in \"The Washington Post\" and then immediately after the article, the Congress called for hearings and the Justice Department to get involved.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "WDT", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 563, "question": "You mean in terms of campaign contributions and things like that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 564, "answer": "Yes, but the general level of corruption that was going on, this is very bad for American politics.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "WP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 571, "question": "What do you want people to feel?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 572, "answer": "I want people to feel is I want them to know what this system is.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "CC", "RB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 585, "question": "What kind of thing do you think is going on that is criminal in your mind?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 586, "answer": "Well, whether it's criminal or not, or it should be criminal maybe is the question.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 592, "question": "What are you doing with your life at the moment?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 593, "answer": "Well, I just finished writing a book.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 595, "question": "Do you have a job at the moment?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 596, "answer": "I don't -- I have a job doing that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "PRP", ",", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 597, "question": "That's it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 598, "answer": "That's it, right now.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 602, "question": "All gone?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 603, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "RB", "IN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 605, "question": "You're aware of that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 606, "answer": "I haven't added it all up, but it was tens of millions.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 607, "question": "All gone?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 608, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 610, "question": "What do you feel about it now that you don't have any?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 611, "answer": "I mean, money is a tool.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 617, "question": "Why did you give it away?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 618, "answer": "Because I felt I got this money to do good things with it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "RB", "RBS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 647, "question": "How did you feel being the butt of the jokes?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 648, "answer": "Well, I have a I have a sense of humor, so most of the time I laughed, if they were good jokes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 657, "question": "How have you explained it to your children?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "TO", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 658, "answer": "Well, I didn't have to explain it to my children.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJS", "."], "qSentId": 666, "question": "What was the single thing you regret most?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJS", "."], "aSentId": 667, "answer": "Well, I don't know that there's a single thing I regret most.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 677, "question": "In all the time that you've been in Congress, how many years now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 678, "answer": "I'm in my 35th.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Congress"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 688, "question": "Is that a good thing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 689, "answer": "No, it's not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "RBR", "JJ", "CC", "RB", "VBN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 703, "question": "And whatever the merits of each of the individual interventions, there comes a point, doesn't there, when if America wants to compete with the likes of China, India and so on, then this constant marching around the world helping everyone has to take a bit of a back seat to helping America?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", ",", "WRB", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "CC", "RB", "IN", ",", "RB", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "NN", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VBG", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 704, "answer": "Well, I think we'll continue, but it will be done in a much more sophisticated and differently organized manner.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America", "China", "India", "America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["United States"]}, "docId": "111112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "NN", ":", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "NN", "NNS", ",", "JJR", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "WP", "MD", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "CC", "VB", "NN", "IN", "CD", "CC", "JJR", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 710, "question": "Who do you think is the biggest threat currently to America?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "RB", "TO", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 711, "answer": "I suspect the problems that are embedded in terrorism -- in other words, cell groups, smaller groups of people who may, in fact, try to transport either a nuclear chemical or biological weapons in some form to the United States and create havoc in one or more of our major cities or through plagues or other diseases.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Romney"]}, "docId": "111112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 714, "question": "Who do you think is emerging, perhaps nobody is yet, as a genuine front-runner candidate?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBZ", "VBG", ",", "RB", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 715, "answer": "Well, I think Governor Romney has been the front-runner throughout this situation.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNS", "TO", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 718, "question": "And can -- if he is, can he beat Barack Obama?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "MD", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 719, "answer": "I would say yes to both.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack Obama"]}}]